<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AutocrossBlog.com - An autocrosser&apos;s blog 24 years in the making! </title>
    <description>Documenting autocross, the finest of all motorsports!</description>
    <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 15:55:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Autocross Trophies, do you need them or want them?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here in the St. Louis region, you used to compete for a trophy at every event you entered. You could stick around after the event, and if you qualified, you would get a trophy to take home. When I started autocrossing, this was my motivation. I wanted to earn a trophy every time I competed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been years since I’ve seen that happen locally, I would guess it has probably been since the middle of the aught’s that the region gave out trophied after an event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trophies varied each year, here are some of the ones I can remember, and you can see some photos of some of them that I still have, 20+ years later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foam Cones, these were some of the best, kids loved them, they were light, easy to transport, and wouldn’t break!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picture Frames with printed place and event information (done for each event).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glass cups, coffee mugs, pint glasses, you name it. These I still have the most of. Have I used them? Nope, have I tossed them out? No way! The logistics of these had to be a nightmare, they were not setup per event, but definitely per placement (1,2,3), and the weight of hauling these around event to event was probably not fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One season had some form of stickers that you could get for trophies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-800-f7890fe2f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Picture Frame Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-200-f7890fe2f.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-400-f7890fe2f.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-800-f7890fe2f.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-1600-f7890fe2f.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-2000-f7890fe2f.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-800-e5ffefdac.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Glass Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-200-e5ffefdac.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-400-e5ffefdac.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-800-e5ffefdac.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-1600-e5ffefdac.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-2000-e5ffefdac.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, year end trophies, that’s where it is really at. In the past some of the coolest ones I received were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embroidered helmet bag&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embroidered gear bag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;National event trophies are a whole topic of their own for another day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-800-0d727445d.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Year End Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-200-0d727445d.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-400-0d727445d.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-800-0d727445d.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-1600-0d727445d.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-2000-0d727445d.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comment below, did you ever get autocross trophies at local events?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are some of your favorites?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post was NOT sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/collections/sps-trophy-shop&quot;&gt;SPS Trophy Shop, but if you’re looking for Autocross Trophies you might want to check them out&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/autocross-trophies</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/autocross-trophies</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>trophies</category>
        
        <category>regions</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Information about the Vitour Tempesta P1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for information on the Vitour Tempesta P1 tire for the sport of autocross you’ve come to the right place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tire isn’t legal for national level autocross competition. Don’t waste your money on it buying a set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-is-selling-vitour-tempesta-p1&quot;&gt;Who is selling Vitour Tempesta P1?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some interneet websites, but not any respectable locations. I wouldn’t recommend placing an order for these any&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-makes-the-vitour-tempesta-p1-tires&quot;&gt;Who makes the Vitour Tempesta P1 tires?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who the f really knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;are-the-vitour-tempesta-p1-tires-legal-at-the-regional-level&quot;&gt;Are the Vitour Tempesta P1 tires legal at the regional level?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some regions, but not in any respectible region. Stick with know and trusted brands, that are legal for national level competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;official-scca-tech-bulletin-information&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.connectsites.net/user_files/scca/downloads/000/070/227/seb_10_28_23mt.pdf?1700513108&quot;&gt;Official SCCA Tech Bulletin Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tech Bulletins&lt;br /&gt;
Event Operations&lt;br /&gt;
#35148 Vitour Tempesta P1 tires&lt;br /&gt;
Under Solo Rules section 13.3, the Vitour Tempesta P1 and XComp H/P are added to the National event tire exclusion list in 13.3.C.4 and under “Wheel and Tire Allowances” in the CAM/XS section of Appendix B, to the CAM/XS tire exclusion list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Due to these being low volume tires from a niche manufacturer, the SEB does not have sufficient information about their performance, actual size(s) availability, and schedule of importation. We do not anticipate having sufficient information to adequately evaluate these tires before January 1st eligibility date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These tires may be removed from the exclusion list when that information becomes available, if all other conditions of 13.3 are met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opinions are my own, and just that, opinions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/vitour-tires-illegal</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/vitour-tires-illegal</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>tires</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 St. Louis Region SCCA Solo Autocross Schedule</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2024 St. Louis Region SCCA Solo Schedule was released just yesterday! It isn’t even up on their website, but we’ve got it here for you now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2024-autocross-schedule&quot;&gt;2024 Autocross Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All events at Family Arena in St. Charles, MO unless otherwise noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 30&lt;/strong&gt; - Novice School&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 7&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 1 (CANCELLED due to lot access)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 21&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 3-5&lt;/strong&gt; - CAM &amp;amp; Event 3 (points event for local region members, and National CAM event)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 9&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 4&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July 21&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 5&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept 8&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept 29&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 7&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oct 20&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the schedule above and make sure to mark your calendars for all the events you want to attend. For any updates to the schedule be sure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://solo.stlscca.org/schedule/&quot;&gt;visit their website&lt;/a&gt; (when they post it)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m working on putting my 2024 schedule together, and I’m excited to see what the St. Louis Region has in store for us this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which events are you planning to attend? Let us know in the comments below!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/2024stlouis-solo-schedule</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/2024stlouis-solo-schedule</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>Schedule</category>
        
        <category>St. Louis</category>
        
        <category>SCCA</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World, AutocrossBlog.com is live!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;AutocrossBlog.com is a culmination of two decades of autocrossing and way too many different cars and car websites over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried to consolidate my car blogs into this one location, I am sure there’s a broken link or two, but this is a good enough start!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be blogging here going forward for all my automotive autocross adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2024 I’ll be back racing in St. Louis and around the Midwest with my good friend Dave Whitworth from &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/autocross-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/autocross-blog</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>Site</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Intersection of Tech and Community: Chris Hammond&apos;s Journey</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-little-about-the-owner-here&quot;&gt;A little about the owner here:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balancing professional pursuits with community involvement isn’t easy, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/&quot;&gt;Chris Hammond&lt;/a&gt; seems to have found the sweet spot. Based in St. Louis, MO, Chris has made significant contributions to his local community, all while advancing his career in the tech industry. Find out more about Chris’ inspiring journey on his personal blog, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/&quot;&gt;ChrisHammond.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/chris-hammond</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/chris-hammond</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project350z 20 Years Ago Today</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;20 Years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been 20 years since I picked up the 350z.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know where it is, I wish I still owned it. Maybe one day Dozzle will let me buy it back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are photos from the day I purchased the car. Actually, this was the day I picked up the car, I went back the next day to sign the papers. I had a date (first date) and the paperwork was taking too long, so Todd (at Bommarito Nissan) told me to come back the next day rather than miss the date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last photo is of the 99 Z-28 that I traded in that day for the 350Z.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-800-14d426070.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-200-14d426070.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-400-14d426070.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-800-14d426070.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-1152-14d426070.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-800-18a175890.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-200-18a175890.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-400-18a175890.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-800-18a175890.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-1152-18a175890.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-800-64d07f26e.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-200-64d07f26e.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-400-64d07f26e.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-800-64d07f26e.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-1152-64d07f26e.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-800-d0923b607.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-200-d0923b607.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-400-d0923b607.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-800-d0923b607.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-1152-d0923b607.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-800-16853f56a.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-200-16853f56a.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-400-16853f56a.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-800-16853f56a.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-1152-16853f56a.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-800-de8241965.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-200-de8241965.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-400-de8241965.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-800-de8241965.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-1152-de8241965.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-800-cc3be3ba0.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-200-cc3be3ba0.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-400-cc3be3ba0.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-800-cc3be3ba0.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-1152-cc3be3ba0.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/20-years-ago-today</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/20-years-ago-today</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for another 240z</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a Datsun 240z in St. Louis!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re selling a project, be sure to let me know! &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:240z@christoc.com&quot;&gt;240z@christoc.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1973 Datsun 240Z, also known as the Nissan Fairlady Z in Japan, is a classic sports car that gained popularity for its sleek design, impressive performance, and affordability. Here is a summary of the car’s history, design, and production details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history&quot;&gt;History:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Datsun 240Z was first introduced in 1969 as a 1970 model, marking the beginning of a line of successful sports cars from Datsun, a subsidiary of Nissan. It was designed to appeal to the American market and was influenced by European sports cars of the era. The 240Z quickly gained a reputation for its powerful performance, striking looks, and accessible price point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 240Z showcased a timeless design that combined elements of a classic sports car with a touch of Japanese styling. Its long hood, short rear deck, and low-slung profile gave it a dynamic and aerodynamic appearance. The sleek body featured flowing lines, a prominent grille, and rounded headlights. The interior provided a driver-focused cockpit with comfortable seating, intuitive controls, and sufficient legroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;engine-and-performance&quot;&gt;Engine and Performance:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the hood, the 1973 240Z featured a 2.4-liter inline-six engine, hence the name 240Z, delivering around 151 horsepower and 146 lb-ft of torque. This engine was known for its smooth power delivery and responsiveness. It was paired with a four-speed manual transmission or an optional three-speed automatic. The 240Z boasted impressive acceleration, excellent handling, and a top speed of around 125 mph (201 km/h), making it a thrilling driving experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;production-numbers&quot;&gt;Production Numbers:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During its production run from 1970 to 1973, Datsun manufactured a total of 30,938 240Z cars for the U.S. market. These numbers include all model years, so it is difficult to pinpoint the exact production figures for the 1973 model alone. However, the 240Z’s overall popularity and high demand contributed to its significant production numbers, making it a successful and iconic sports car of its time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1973 Datsun 240Z remains highly regarded by enthusiasts and collectors today for its timeless design, engaging driving experience, and historical significance as one of the pioneers of Japanese sports cars.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/st-louis-240z</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/st-louis-240z</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why you should autocross</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Autocross is an exciting and challenging motorsport that is quickly gaining popularity among car enthusiasts. It is a competitive event where drivers navigate a course that is laid out on a large parking lot or closed-off airfield. The objective is to complete the course in the fastest time possible, while navigating tight turns, hairpin bends, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.specfrs.com/autocross-accident-why-you-need-autocross-insurance&quot;&gt;other obstacles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best things about autocross is that it is accessible to a wide range of drivers. Whether you are a seasoned pro or a beginner, there is a class for you. This means that you can compete against drivers of similar skill levels, which makes for a fair and enjoyable competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great thing about autocross is that it is relatively inexpensive. All you need is a car, some safety gear, and a desire to have fun. You do not need a high-powered or expensive racecar to participate. Many people use their daily drivers, which keeps the cost of entry low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most important things you need to participate in autocross is a good set of tires. Tires are the only point of contact between your car and the ground, and they play a crucial role in your car’s performance. Good tires will provide better traction, which will help you navigate the course faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt; is a great place to buy your autocross supplies, including tires. They have a wide range of tires that are specifically designed for autocross, so you can be sure that you are getting the best possible product. They also offer a variety of other autocross supplies such as suspension upgrades, brakes, and other performance parts that can help you to improve your car’s performance on the course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to providing high-quality autocross supplies, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt; also offers great customer service. They have a team of knowledgeable and experienced staff who can help you to find the right products for your car and your driving style. They also offer installation services, so you can have your new parts installed quickly and easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a fun and exciting motorsport that is accessible to a wide range of drivers, then autocross is definitely worth considering. It is a great way to push yourself and your car to the limit, and it is also a great way to meet new people and make friends. And if you are looking for high-quality autocross supplies, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt; is the place to go. They have everything you need to get started, and their customer service is second to none. So why not give it a try? You won’t regret it!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/why-you-should-autocross</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/why-you-should-autocross</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>FR-S</category>
        
        <category>SSC</category>
        
        <category>Setup</category>
        
        <category>Accident</category>
        
        <category>Supplies</category>
        
        <category>Gear</category>
        
        <category>St. Louis</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Race Gear in St. Louis Missouri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt; is your one stop shop for all your autocross needs. They have a huge selection of tires, wheels, and suspension parts.  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com&quot;&gt;They are located in St. Louis, MO&lt;/a&gt;, but they ship all over the country. They are a great resource for all your autocross needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for Race Gear in St. Louis, &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/pages/find-us-service-info&quot;&gt;be sure to stop by the SPS at their retail location&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/race-gear-in-st-louis</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/race-gear-in-st-louis</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>FR-S</category>
        
        <category>SSC</category>
        
        <category>Setup</category>
        
        <category>Accident</category>
        
        <category>Supplies</category>
        
        <category>Gear</category>
        
        <category>St. Louis</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to buy a race helmet in St. Louis?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for a racing helmet in St. Louis Missouri, you should be looking at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.soloperformance.com/&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SPS has a large number of different helmet makes models and sizes that you can try on in their retail store. Here’s a link to &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/pages/find-us-service-info&quot;&gt;visit their St Louis location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;do-i-need-to-try-on-my-helmet&quot;&gt;Do I need to try on my helmet?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trying on your helmet is important, you want to make sure what you select fits you properly, and is comfortable. You’ll be wearing it for a long time, so you want to make sure it’s comfortable. You also shouldn’t just buy the cheapest helmet you can find, but what you can afford. We’re talking about protecting your noggin, I assume that is important to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-brand-helmet-do-i-need&quot;&gt;What brand helmet do I need?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brand specifics will obviously vary, do you need/want the most expensive coolest looking helmet? Or do you need the one that does the job the best? My recommendation is you try on multiple brands and see which one feels best, and meets your budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;can-i-buy-a-helmet-online&quot;&gt;Can I buy a helmet online?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Absolutely you can buy a helmet online. &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/collections/helmets-and-accessories&quot;&gt;SoloPerformance.com&lt;/a&gt; has one of the largest selections of helmets online, they sell hundreds of helmets a year.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/where-to-get-a-race-helmet-in-st-louis</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.AutocrossBlog.com/where-to-get-a-race-helmet-in-st-louis</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
