<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AutocrossBlog.com</title>
    <description>Documenting autocross, the finest of all motorsports!</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:45:55 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:45:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Cones to Camaraderie: Recap of St. Louis&apos;s First Autocross of 2024</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first local autocross of the year was officially Event #2 for the St. Louis Region SCCA. Why Event #2 if it was the first? Event #1 ended up getting scrapped due to lot availability issues and the committee just left the original titles of the events the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure when I last ran a regional event; it was likely back in 2022 when I drove Matt Miller’s Camaro at Gateway, where the car nearly caused a serious accident by heading straight for some jersey barriers and a fence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;event-overview&quot;&gt;Event Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Showing up to the event in the morning, I knew what to expect, I’ve run locally in St. Louis since 2000, so things shouldn’t be that much different. The event had 155 drivers pre-registered, so coming into the day you have to assume a few things, being the first event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) There will be delays
2) There will be newbies getting lost
3) You will be there longer than you want to be
4) You will have fun&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the event ran pretty smoothly, a few timing issues, many of which I think were caused by workers running through the finish. Things will smooth out as people get the rust off, and newbies start to learn how things work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ProTip:&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re working in the timing van, and you see someone run through the finish lights, essentially tripping a finish when a car hasn’t ran through the lights, there’s a button on the timer called “Reset Finish”, if you’re fast enough, you can hit that button BEFORE the next car comes through the finish and you’ll save yourself, and everyone else, a lot of headache with timing issues. If you aren’t able to do this quickly, don’t fret; it takes time to get comfortable with some of these tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-people&quot;&gt;The People&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was great to catch up with folks I haven’t seen in a few years! Thanks to everyone who said hello to me. I thought about trying to list off all the folks I hadn’t seen in a while, but I am positive I would forget someone and I don’t want to do that, so, no names, but it was great to see you all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;working-the-course&quot;&gt;Working the Course&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ended up working at Corner 4 in the first heat. I haven’t ran that much in quite a while and am paying for that with full on body pains today! This corner was the Chicago box followed by a non-optional 3 cone slalom before the finish. The first couple of runs people didn’t hit too many cones, but as they started pushing, all the cones in the Chicago box and the slalom started to suffer. One guy came out while we were working and scolded us for not seeing that a cone was out of position in the slalom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ProTip:&lt;/strong&gt; Just call this out over the radio so that course workers can be informed and fix it, no need to walk out on the course yourself to do something to the course. To be honest, that’s probably grounds for disqualification…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-course&quot;&gt;The Course&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ouch, let me start off by saying, I have never turned so much at an autocross on the family arena parking lot as I did on the course yesterday. I am not sure I would define this as fun in a 2012 Mustang. We were the fastest car on the course? Certainly! Could it have been a more enjoyable experience? Absofrickenlutely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-results&quot;&gt;The Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dave and I ran second heat in CAM-C. I started out running a time of 55.* with a cone, which based on the times I had noticed while working the course seemed to be a decent starting point. My second run I managed to drop a second off to get down to a 54.3* while Dave put down a 55.4* on his second run. Third run I managed to get to a 54.333 which would end up being my fastest, while Dave put down a 54.5. Fourth runs we both put down slower times, and then on our fifth and final runs we each put down a 54.1*, with Dave running a 54.162 to my 54.105, the catch being that I had a cone on my 5th run to negate the improvement and give Dave the win again for the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am never really happy when I don’t finish on top of PAX results, it’s been a while since that has occurred, but I look forward to hopefully achieving that goal a few times in 2024…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-photos&quot;&gt;The Photos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I was working first heat, running second heat, I was only able to shoot photos of the third heat, but I managed to take 1300 photos during that time. &lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3&quot;&gt;I have posted 300 of those photos on my RainbowMarks Photography event gallery, check it out and purchase a shot or two if you ran third&lt;/a&gt;! If you ran first or second heat, sorry! Hopefully at some point this year I’ll get an opportunity to take pictures of every driver. (Perhaps at the CAM Challenge in two weeks!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3/i-3QpjpSz/buy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-2-600-bb1264ed6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Street Creature Mustang splitter digging into the pavement&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-2-200-bb1264ed6.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-2-400-bb1264ed6.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-2-600-bb1264ed6.jpg 600w&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3/i-p7Z8Bkd/buy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-800-bedaa3eb8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Subaru Wagon lifting the inside rear tire&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-200-bedaa3eb8.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-400-bedaa3eb8.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-800-bedaa3eb8.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-1600-bedaa3eb8.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-3-2000-bedaa3eb8.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3/i-gXFDg6V/buy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-800-9382a2e63.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;White Mustang attempting the drift&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-200-9382a2e63.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-400-9382a2e63.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-800-9382a2e63.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-1600-9382a2e63.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-4-2000-9382a2e63.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.rainbowmarks.com/2024/Autocross/St-Louis-Region-SCCA/4-21-2024-Event-2/Heat-3/i-B5DVhgx/buy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-800-6567c1e87.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;White Mustang paying for the attempted drift&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-200-6567c1e87.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-400-6567c1e87.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-800-6567c1e87.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-1600-6567c1e87.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/April/StLouis/Event2-5-2000-6567c1e87.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-next&quot;&gt;What’s next?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CAM Challenge is coming up here in less than two weeks, once again at the Family Arena in St. Charles, MO. If you haven’t signed up yet, get signed up! Local entrants not running in CAM classes (or the X classes) can run for $45 for the weekend, with 6 runs on Saturday and 3 runs on Sunday! CAM/X drivers can enter for $125 entry with the same 9 runs but also the ability to qualify for the Challenge portion after the Sunday morning runs. If you’ve not run a SCCA National level event before, this is the perfect time to try it out. You’ll see drivers that are way faster than what you’ll find at typical location regional event, and if you’re local to STL you get to do it without all the travel costs! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.motorsportreg.com/events/2024-tire-rack-scca-st-louis-cam-challenge-family-arena-national-solo-360805&quot;&gt;Sign Up Today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;videos-of-runs&quot;&gt;Videos of Runs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the video of my fastest autocross run, followed by Dave’s fastest run from Sunday April 21st, 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0D6l2NeEKIQ?si=RBDpT7xErAyxNMLS&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/akpxKxMThFg?si=W93EiJLfHGobQjFM&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/st-louis-autocross-event-2-2024</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/st-louis-autocross-event-2-2024</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>National Tour</category>
        
        <category>SCCA</category>
        
        <category>Mustang</category>
        
        <category>Friends</category>
        
        <category>St. Louis</category>
        
        <category>Local</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Hills National Tour Results</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.autocrossblog.com/roadtrip-to-moultrie&quot;&gt;Last Thursday I wrote a blog post about the trip down to Moultrie Georgia for the 2024 Red Hills Solo National Tour&lt;/a&gt;, this post will serve as the event review from the event. My first National Tour event in a number of years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Moultrie late Thursday night and got checked in to our hotel. The lot was exceptionally small, so getting the truck and trailer situated took Dave some work, but fortunately being a Thursday night there weren’t many customer vehicles on the lot, so we had plenty of room for the rig.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event was held at Spence Field just outside of Moultrie. Probably 30-40 miles from the South Georgia Motorsports Park where previous tours have been held (and attended by myself). Spence Field is an old WWII air field that was used for advanced pilot training. Since the war it has served a number of purposes, it’s most prominent use being host of one of the largest Agriculture expos held every fall. Driving into the property feels very familiar to those initiated in autocross and old air fields, similar to Walnut Ridge, Lincoln and many other autocross sites that I’ve visited over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday we pretty much woke up to wetness in Georgia. It rained off and on throughout the day. This made the idea of the practice course not all that interesting, but I knew I needed to get out there anyways. I ended up taking 3 runs. The first run I spun. The second run was okay. The third run I spun and saw the Mustang sliding into a light pole… No more practice runs for me, blood pressure too high after that scare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday evening I went out for 2 course walks. By this time my feet were thoroughly soaked, and I managed to give myself a nice big ole blister on my big toe on the right foot which then bothered me for the rest of the weekend. Reminder: Put some damn waterproof shoes in my autocross box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning we got up, had breakfast at the hotel, their continental breakfast left a little to be desired, but they did have some decent sausage biscuits that you could get and heat up. From there a quick stop at the gas station to grab a coffee and supplies for the day before heading out to the event site, waiting for the sun to come up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another couple of course walks really set my blistered feet on fire for the day. Second Reminder: Waterproof shoes, dry socks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My work assignment for the weekend was to be Sweep for the second heat. For the uninitiated, sweep is the car that goes out half way though each run (3 runs per heat, 6 sweep runs) to grab the paper corner sheets in which a corner worker writes down every car that goes passed, and which cones (if any) that car hit. This is something done at National Events, and sweep brings the sheets in so that if a driver has a question they can look at the corner sheets to see which specific cone they hit on a previous run. Super helpful when you aren’t sure if/where you hit a cone. This was my first time doing sweep, in 24 years, I had Evan Williams riding along with me as the worker chief, he actually did most of the work, grabbing and organizing the papers, I just did the driving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time the third heat came around I was ready to go. I had setup two GoPros on the top of the car, but was unable to get them working properly with the remote, I figured out the new Hero12 was setup to shut off after 5 minutes of inactivity, which meant I needed to keep changing the mode every so often or it would shut off, so I missed the forward facing video of my first run, and the SoloStorm error’d out connecting to the Hero4 that Dave uses with that setup. I did however manage to get a rear facing video of that run. The run started out exciting, I looped the car right after the start line and put the nose off into the grass. No harm no foul. I ended up with a time of something like 58 seconds, which I figured was 10+ seconds off from where I should have been on the first run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;saturday-run-1&quot;&gt;Saturday Run 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/P51JlEntKU0?si=xZigZtenp-H74_8l&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second run was much better, good enough for second place, about .5 behind Dave’s best run which would come on his third run. My third run however, was wet. How so? Somehow it started raining as I got into the car for my third run, and then pulling up to the line and starting it started raining harder, enough to make the ground slick and cause me to be about 2 seconds slower than my second run. Still good enough for second, but not near as close to Dave as I would need to be for Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;saturday-run-2&quot;&gt;Saturday Run 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6nIdPuJmTRg?si=JlG5YgKCKCE5SHy5&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday evening the local region provided Pizzas for dinner, I am NOT a fan of cold pizza, so I was right near the front of the line and was pleasantly surprised that I enjoyed the Marcos deliver they brought in. Kudos to the Red Hills region for a great dinner experience!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave, Beth and Sean all went out for a course walk after dinner, I didn’t dare attempt that on Saturday evening due to the pain I was feeling in my feet, I was hoping that I would be a bit better Sunday morning and get a couple of course walks in before Sunday runs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately my feet did feel a tad better for those Sunday course walks, I managed to get 2 walks in before first heat. My feet definitely paid the price, but I was glad to see the course in Sunday’s direction, which was reverse of the course from Saturday with a few minor changes at the start and finish lines to configure for reverse running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday competition runs definitely started out better, my first run I was about a tenth of a second faster than Dave, second run was even faster for me, but I managed to hit a cone entering the final turnaround. I wasn’t sure where I had hit the cone, so I ran over to the area where they kept the corner sheets to try to track down what I hit. On Dave’s second run he was a tenth of a second faster than my dirty run was at 44.589+1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew I needed to put a good clean, fast, run down on my third run, so I went out and did what I could. Putting in a 44.099, not quite the 43 I was looking for, and not enough to catch Dave for the lead in CAM-C. Dave went out on his third run and put a 44.155 down, giving him an overall victory of .486. Here’s a video of both of our third runs from Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DaGppirxdhk?si=BOwHLthesa38EGqb&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promptly after third runs were done I started packing things up for the trip home. Dave and Beth planned to make the drive over 2 days, getting home later on Monday, so I hopped in with Sean and Melissa to make the full drive home. Big thanks to both of them, and Dave and Beth, for putting up with me over the weekend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I was pleased with how I did for my first real event in almost a year, and first time driving the Mustang since September 2021. I look forward to getting more adjusted to the ride and seeing how else the rest of the year goes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s next? A local event on the 21st of April, then the CAM Challenge in St. Charles, MO the first weekend of May.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 10:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/red-hills-national-tour</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/red-hills-national-tour</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>National Tour</category>
        
        <category>SCCA</category>
        
        <category>Mustang</category>
        
        <category>Friends</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roadtrip to Moultrie</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;solonatshasstarted&quot;&gt;#SOLONATSHASSTARTED&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here we go. We are on the road south to Moultrie, Georgia for the 2024 Tire Rack SCCA Red Hills National Tour at Spence Field. I met Dave and Beth at Solo Performance this morning and we hit the road just after 7am, with the plan of getting all the way to Moultrie today, Thursday the 21st. This will be my first time to Moultrie, after having run a few times when the National Tour events were held in Adel, GA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three of us will be driving their 2012 Mustang GT in CAM-C this weekend. I’ve driven this car many times throughout the years, the last time being at Nationals in 2021. It is the car I got my first trophy at Nationals (5th place), back in 2013 when RTR was a thing (street tire index class before 200 treadware street tire were the rules for Street/Stock classes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be my first National Tour out of town in a while, I am having trouble remembering exactly when, probably 2019? I attended some ProSolo events in that time, but can’t think of a Tour that I attended since probably Spring Nationals 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward to running the SPS Mustang in CAM-C this season at as many local and out of town events that I can make work. Scheduling around kids events these days has become more difficult as the kids get older, I am looking forward to them being able to join me at Autocross starting in the next couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates from Moultrie this weekend and look for some links to photos from the event, assuming I get time to take pictures when not running or working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Chris&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/roadtrip-to-moultrie</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/roadtrip-to-moultrie</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>National Tour</category>
        
        <category>SCCA</category>
        
        <category>Mustang</category>
        
        <category>Friends</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Autocross Trophies, do you need them or want them?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here in the St. Louis region, you used to compete for a trophy at every event you entered. You could stick around after the event, and if you qualified, you would get a trophy to take home. When I started autocrossing, this was my motivation. I wanted to earn a trophy every time I competed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been years since I’ve seen that happen locally, I would guess it has probably been since the middle of the aught’s that the region gave out trophied after an event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trophies varied each year, here are some of the ones I can remember, and you can see some photos of some of them that I still have, 20+ years later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foam Cones, these were some of the best, kids loved them, they were light, easy to transport, and wouldn’t break!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Picture Frames with printed place and event information (done for each event).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glass cups, coffee mugs, pint glasses, you name it. These I still have the most of. Have I used them? Nope, have I tossed them out? No way! The logistics of these had to be a nightmare, they were not setup per event, but definitely per placement (1,2,3), and the weight of hauling these around event to event was probably not fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One season had some form of stickers that you could get for trophies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-800-f7890fe2f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Picture Frame Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-200-f7890fe2f.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-400-f7890fe2f.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-800-f7890fe2f.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-1600-f7890fe2f.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-1-2000-f7890fe2f.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-800-e5ffefdac.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Glass Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-200-e5ffefdac.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-400-e5ffefdac.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-800-e5ffefdac.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-1600-e5ffefdac.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-2-2000-e5ffefdac.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, year end trophies, that’s where it is really at. In the past some of the coolest ones I received were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embroidered helmet bag&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embroidered gear bag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;National event trophies are a whole topic of their own for another day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-800-0d727445d.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Autocross Year End Trophies&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-200-0d727445d.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-400-0d727445d.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-800-0d727445d.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-1600-0d727445d.jpg 1600w, /assets/images_out/2024/February/AutocrossTrophies/AutocrossTrophies-3-2000-0d727445d.jpg 2000w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comment below, did you ever get autocross trophies at local events?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are some of your favorites?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post was NOT sponsored by &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/collections/sps-trophy-shop&quot;&gt;SPS Trophy Shop, but if you’re looking for Autocross Trophies you might want to check them out&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 07:00:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/autocross-trophies</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/autocross-trophies</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>trophies</category>
        
        <category>regions</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Information about the Vitour Tempesta P1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for information on the Vitour Tempesta P1 tire for the sport of autocross you’ve come to the right place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tire isn’t legal for national level autocross competition. Don’t waste your money on it buying a set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-is-selling-vitour-tempesta-p1&quot;&gt;Who is selling Vitour Tempesta P1?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some interneet websites, but not any respectable locations. I wouldn’t recommend placing an order for these any&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-makes-the-vitour-tempesta-p1-tires&quot;&gt;Who makes the Vitour Tempesta P1 tires?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who the f really knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;are-the-vitour-tempesta-p1-tires-legal-at-the-regional-level&quot;&gt;Are the Vitour Tempesta P1 tires legal at the regional level?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some regions, but not in any respectible region. Stick with know and trusted brands, that are legal for national level competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;official-scca-tech-bulletin-information&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.connectsites.net/user_files/scca/downloads/000/070/227/seb_10_28_23mt.pdf?1700513108&quot;&gt;Official SCCA Tech Bulletin Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tech Bulletins&lt;br /&gt;
Event Operations&lt;br /&gt;
#35148 Vitour Tempesta P1 tires&lt;br /&gt;
Under Solo Rules section 13.3, the Vitour Tempesta P1 and XComp H/P are added to the National event tire exclusion list in 13.3.C.4 and under “Wheel and Tire Allowances” in the CAM/XS section of Appendix B, to the CAM/XS tire exclusion list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Due to these being low volume tires from a niche manufacturer, the SEB does not have sufficient information about their performance, actual size(s) availability, and schedule of importation. We do not anticipate having sufficient information to adequately evaluate these tires before January 1st eligibility date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These tires may be removed from the exclusion list when that information becomes available, if all other conditions of 13.3 are met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opinions are my own, and just that, opinions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:00:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/vitour-tires-illegal</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/vitour-tires-illegal</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>Tires</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2024 St. Louis Region SCCA Solo Autocross Schedule</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2024 St. Louis Region SCCA Solo Schedule was released just yesterday! It isn’t even up on their website, but we’ve got it here for you now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2024-autocross-schedule&quot;&gt;2024 Autocross Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All events at Family Arena in St. Charles, MO unless otherwise noted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 30&lt;/strong&gt; - Novice School&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 7&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 1 (CANCELLED due to lot access)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 21&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 3-5&lt;/strong&gt; - CAM &amp;amp; Event 3 (points event for local region members, and National CAM event)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;June 9&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 4&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;July 21&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 5&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept 8&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 6&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept 29&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 7&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oct 20&lt;/strong&gt; - Event 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the schedule above and make sure to mark your calendars for all the events you want to attend. For any updates to the schedule be sure to &lt;a href=&quot;https://solo.stlscca.org/schedule/&quot;&gt;visit their website&lt;/a&gt; (when they post it)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m working on putting my 2024 schedule together, and I’m excited to see what the St. Louis Region has in store for us this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which events are you planning to attend? Let us know in the comments below!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 04:00:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024stlouis-solo-schedule</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024stlouis-solo-schedule</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>Schedule</category>
        
        <category>St. Louis</category>
        
        <category>SCCA</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World, AutocrossBlog.com is live!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;AutocrossBlog.com is a culmination of two decades of autocrossing and way too many different cars and car websites over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried to consolidate my car blogs into this one location, I am sure there’s a broken link or two, but this is a good enough start!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be blogging here going forward for all my automotive autocross adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2024 I’ll be back racing in St. Louis and around the Midwest with my good friend Dave Whitworth from &lt;a href=&quot;https://soloperformance.com/&quot;&gt;Solo Performance Specialties&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 04:00:15 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/autocross-blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/autocross-blog</guid>
        
        
        <category>Autocross</category>
        
        <category>Site</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Intersection of Tech and Community: Chris Hammond&apos;s Journey</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-little-about-the-owner-here&quot;&gt;A little about the owner here:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balancing professional pursuits with community involvement isn’t easy, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/&quot;&gt;Chris Hammond&lt;/a&gt; seems to have found the sweet spot. Based in St. Louis, MO, Chris has made significant contributions to his local community, all while advancing his career in the tech industry. Find out more about Chris’ inspiring journey on his personal blog, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chrishammond.com/&quot;&gt;ChrisHammond.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 05:00:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/chris-hammond</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/chris-hammond</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project350z 20 Years Ago Today</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;20 Years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been 20 years since I picked up the 350z.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know where it is, I wish I still owned it. Maybe one day Dozzle will let me buy it back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are photos from the day I purchased the car. Actually, this was the day I picked up the car, I went back the next day to sign the papers. I had a date (first date) and the paperwork was taking too long, so Todd (at Bommarito Nissan) told me to come back the next day rather than miss the date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last photo is of the 99 Z-28 that I traded in that day for the 350Z.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-800-14d426070.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-200-14d426070.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-400-14d426070.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-800-14d426070.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-1-1152-14d426070.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-800-18a175890.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-200-18a175890.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-400-18a175890.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-800-18a175890.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-2-1152-18a175890.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-800-64d07f26e.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-200-64d07f26e.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-400-64d07f26e.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-800-64d07f26e.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-3-1152-64d07f26e.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-800-d0923b607.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-200-d0923b607.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-400-d0923b607.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-800-d0923b607.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-4-1152-d0923b607.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-800-16853f56a.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-200-16853f56a.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-400-16853f56a.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-800-16853f56a.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-5-1152-16853f56a.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-800-de8241965.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-200-de8241965.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-400-de8241965.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-800-de8241965.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-6-1152-de8241965.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-800-cc3be3ba0.jpg&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-200-cc3be3ba0.jpg 200w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-400-cc3be3ba0.jpg 400w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-800-cc3be3ba0.jpg 800w, /assets/images_out/April2003/April2003-7-1152-cc3be3ba0.jpg 1152w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 05:00:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/20-years-ago-today</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/20-years-ago-today</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for another 240z</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a Datsun 240z in St. Louis!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re selling a project, be sure to let me know! &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:240z@christoc.com&quot;&gt;240z@christoc.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1973 Datsun 240Z, also known as the Nissan Fairlady Z in Japan, is a classic sports car that gained popularity for its sleek design, impressive performance, and affordability. Here is a summary of the car’s history, design, and production details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history&quot;&gt;History:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Datsun 240Z was first introduced in 1969 as a 1970 model, marking the beginning of a line of successful sports cars from Datsun, a subsidiary of Nissan. It was designed to appeal to the American market and was influenced by European sports cars of the era. The 240Z quickly gained a reputation for its powerful performance, striking looks, and accessible price point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 240Z showcased a timeless design that combined elements of a classic sports car with a touch of Japanese styling. Its long hood, short rear deck, and low-slung profile gave it a dynamic and aerodynamic appearance. The sleek body featured flowing lines, a prominent grille, and rounded headlights. The interior provided a driver-focused cockpit with comfortable seating, intuitive controls, and sufficient legroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;engine-and-performance&quot;&gt;Engine and Performance:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the hood, the 1973 240Z featured a 2.4-liter inline-six engine, hence the name 240Z, delivering around 151 horsepower and 146 lb-ft of torque. This engine was known for its smooth power delivery and responsiveness. It was paired with a four-speed manual transmission or an optional three-speed automatic. The 240Z boasted impressive acceleration, excellent handling, and a top speed of around 125 mph (201 km/h), making it a thrilling driving experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;production-numbers&quot;&gt;Production Numbers:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During its production run from 1970 to 1973, Datsun manufactured a total of 30,938 240Z cars for the U.S. market. These numbers include all model years, so it is difficult to pinpoint the exact production figures for the 1973 model alone. However, the 240Z’s overall popularity and high demand contributed to its significant production numbers, making it a successful and iconic sports car of its time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1973 Datsun 240Z remains highly regarded by enthusiasts and collectors today for its timeless design, engaging driving experience, and historical significance as one of the pioneers of Japanese sports cars.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:37:30 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/st-louis-240z</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/st-louis-240z</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
